[September 25, 1999]
I came to Australia when I was five.
My life hasn't been easy.
And I thought of committing suicide so many times.
But I thought, you know, I've got to put up with it
because I have to get revenge on my parents
who threw me out just like garbage.
I was about 9 when I was adopted from the orphanage.
Korean? Yeah, I know the language but I don't use it.
I don't even want to think about the goddamn country.
What would I say to my mother
who abandoned me if I met her?
Go to hell!
Don't remember. I was adopted when I was two.
[Danny Anderson
- Korean name: Cha Muhyeok (age 22)]
Korean? I'm great at it. My girlfriend taught me.
"Oh, my goodness!" "Gosh darn it!" "Yes!"
I know all those phrases.
This is my girlfriend Jiyeong.
To my mother? I understand.
She probably had her reasons.
No one would ditch their child like that.
Stuff happens.
Maybe she was too poor to even feed me milk
and gave me up so I could have a better life.
Tommy!
Bad boy. Sit. Sit!
I'll meet my poor mother one day.
I'll buy her some pretty clothes,
some BBQ meat, and a beautiful house.
Mom, I'll go there and let you live in luxury.
Just wait five years!
Just five years! Okay?
It was good but this guy doesn't
match our show concept.
I know, right?
And why can't he speak proper Korean? Annoying.
I'll do some editing.
Don't you have better footage?
I'll look for some.
[Special Program: Overseas Adoptions
-  "I Hate Korea" Editing in Session]
[Episode 1]
[Five years later...]
Hello. Do you need help?
- Where are you from?
- Japan.
[Speaking Japanese] Really? Nice to meet you.
I'm also Japanese.
You are? Nice to meet you.
What a relief!
Get in. I'll drive you.
Really? Thank you!
Thank you. Thank you.
I came here on a trip but my English is lousy.
I'd been worrying so much.
Thank goodness.
Leave your bag and get out the car quietly, girl.
You rotten bastards! Give back my bags!
Dang! We got some dough now!
What the hell? Two is missing.
Make sure you split half. Before I cut your hands off.
Yeah, we got some dough now! It's time to party!
- I need it for something else.
- What?
Jiyeong's gift. It's my wife's birthday tomorrow.
Hello, Kang Minju!
I'm Song from "Behind The Camera News."
Apparently the rumors that you two
got married are true?
Congratulations.
Thanks. "Behind the Camera"
informants are really incredible.
Hey, lady. Married? Who got married?
- Aren't we getting married?
- What?
Were you just playing with me then?
We did it!
Thanks, Eunchae!
I'm not doing this again.
I'm serious. Do this to me again...
and I'll never speak to you again.
Alright.
You should settle down already.
Live and love one man. Stop being such a floozy.
Hey, Kang Minju!
Song Eunchae! What do you think love is?
To me, love's just a game.
Like Starcraft.
Hey, baby! How have you been?
Sure. Let's meet there.
I'm in the middle of filming, so I'll see you later.
Honey!
No, I'm not busy.
Don't you miss me?
[I don't want to live, Eunchae From: Our Star]
[The only phone superstars
Choi Yun & Kang Minju use!]
Choi Yun!
Come in. I'm in the bathroom.
Get in! What are you doing?
What's the matter now? Why don't you want to live?
She ignored my text.
Even though I sent her two.
But it's not broken.
What did you send?
"I'm looking forward to our trip together."
Is it corny?
I want to become your special someone!
That's corny, huh?
Cheesy, huh?
Hey, Song Eunchae!
It won't work out with Minju.
Why not?
It's just... I don't think she's right for you.
So... You're saying I'm not in her league?
No, not that...
Whatever.
So embarrassing...
I just wanna die!
Yun!
Oh, Yun!
Yun, Yun! Yun!
I trust only you, Song Eunchae!
Help make Kang Minju mine no matter what!
Come on, help me out!
She always listens to everything you say. Come on.
Fine.
Oh, my!
Hey, do you see me as a man?
Go in and wash, too.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
- Do you wanna get out of here?
- Yeah.
Just leave it. I got it.
This dress... Can you wrap it?
That dress is very expensive.
This is enough, right?
- Give me your hand, baby. You like?
- I love it.
- You like?
- I love it. Thank you, Jason.
- It looks beautiful.
- Thanks.
What else would you like, baby?
That's beautiful, that dress over there...
Sorry. Please understand.
Jason is waiting.
I'll get going.
I love you!
I love you, Jiyeong!
I do, too.
I love you more than anything in the world.
But... I love Jason's money more.
I hope to see you at my wedding.
[I'm Sorry, I Love You]
What's on the schedule for today?
We'll film an ad today, followed by some TV interviews.
Okay.
Great job, thank you!
Hang it over there.
Yun.
How was your day?
It was good.
One moment!
- Minju?
- Eunchae, come here.
What's up?
Ta-da!
- What is that?
- Wine.
You know, the Napoleon sort of wine...
A present from a fan!
Wow!
Wanna come over to my hotel tonight?
Let's drink it together.
Sure! Why not?
Can I be included?
Is it alright if I include myself?
If you come, the honor will be mine.
Eunchae! Come together today!
Sure.
Is love like Starcraft to you, too?
What?
Is love a game to you, too?
Who says love is like Starcraft?
Minju?
No. Just someone I know.
Don't hang out with that person, whoever it is.
My innocent Eunchae! Are you in shock?
Can't you also think of love as a game?
If the person you love ever betrays you...
Or destroys you inside, try not to be hurt by it.
Does that work for you?
Yes!
Yun!
Yun! Yun!
Eunchae!
Yun, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Does it hurt?
It burns, doesn't it?
Doesn't he know how to drive?
That bastard is dead meat if I catch him.
- It's fine...
- How is it fine?
Shouldn't you see a doctor?
I'm fine!
What do you mean you're fine?
You're still so young and
your face is a mess. It's not fine!
Let me see your face.
This might become a scar.
How can a pretty face have scars?
This is so depressing to me.
Yun...
Need to go to the bathroom? Want me to escort you?
No! Minju's probably waiting.
I don't think I can go like this.
So wanna go by yourself?
How can I leave you alone when you're like this?
Go. You want to, don't you?
Hey, how can I leave you here, huh?
Take off your clothes...
You probably have other scrapes.
I'll bandage them for you.
Just go. People will get the wrong idea.
Let them get the wrong idea.
If a scandal breaks out, we can just marry.
I want to sleep. I'm sleepy.
Want to hear a lullaby?
♪ Love me tender ♪
You don't have to...
Just listen!
Korea's number one singer is singing you a lullaby.
♪ Love me tender ♪
♪ Love me sweet ♪
♪ Never let me go ♪
♪ You have made my life complete ♪
♪ And I love you so ♪
Sleeping?
Eunchae. Are you sleeping?
Yeah, Minju. It's Yu.
I'll be there now. It's not too late, right?
Also, stay behind tomorrow.
Just do it.
Tell your manager to go back first, and stay behind.
All right?
Hi, need some help?
Airport...
- Airport?
- Thank you! Thank you!
- Thanks.
- You're welcome, sir.
Eunchae!
Song Eunchae!
Something came up. I'm heading back to Seoul.
See you in Seoul!
You left without a goodbye?
Thieves! Robbers!
You bastards!
Eunchae left this morning?
Yeah...
Why so suddenly?
She was supposed to hang out with me.
I should be going back then, too.
Can you change my flight to today?
I told you to stay behind!
What about me?
Am I not here?
Don't you see me?
I see you.
But... I love Jason's money more.
Are you Japanese? I'm Japanese.
Are you Chinese? I live in Chinatown, too.
You Korean?
You're Korean?
I'm saved!
Saved!
Tastes so good.
It's okay.
Love is just a game to me.
Like Starcraft.
Starcraft...
Stay right here. I'll be back in no time.
Okay. Goodbye!
- Give me more.
- Not more.
- Come on.
- All right, one more. Just one more.
Thank you.
Hi, darling. How are you?
Hi. How have you been?
Thank you. Thank you.
Check these out, man. What's that, man?
Come on up on stage. Come on.
Auction! Come on up on stage.
Let's go, let's go.
Auction! Come on!
How much? $700? I hear $200!
$400!
A million dollars!
Where'd you go? If you had come any later...
Hey!
Mister!
Hey, dude!
Hey, mophead!
How beautiful! It's like a painting.
Be my girlfriend.
Perhaps I should abandon everything and live here.
For the past three years, I could only think of you.
I like you.
Years from now, when I die, I'll come here to die.
We can't.
What?
Since you're the person my friend Eunchae
most cherishes.
You and me can't.
What do you mean?
Because Eunchae treats you
like her own flesh and blood.
Instead of a flirt like me, meet a good woman.
I swear I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die right here!
Hey! Choi Yun!
Choi Yun!
Choi Yun! Yun!
Minju!
Choi Yun!
You're sleeping here?
Don't you have a home?
Mommy!
Mommy! Ahh!
Hey!
Hey, Mister!
Danny, how you going, man? Who's your girlfriend?
- Get out of here.
- Alright man, cool it.
Let's go.
Mom...
I have a husband! I'm married! With children!
Just go to sleep!
Unless you want to die.
Oh, no...
You okay? You alright?
Are you coming to your senses?
How embarrassing.
I'm going to kill myself.
I'm going to bury my face in the sand and die.
I'm going to die! Drink all the
ocean's water and explode!
I gave you fair warning.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Wow, it's my bag!
[Start paying attenshun crazee brat]
The color sucks. It sucks.
Give it here!
A guy who can't even shave.
Like this and like this...
You have to go slowly...
Okay. I'll do it.
It's okay. I'll do it all for you.
You just stay put.
I'll groom your hair, and I'll dress you.
I'll do everything for you, okay, baby?
Come here!
Oh, save me!
Don't! Stop it!
- Where's the bride?
- I don't know. Who are you?
Where's the bride? I was told that she was here!
How did you get in here?
Muhyeok?
I ate all the kimchi.
What?
I ate all the kimchi. Why didn't you make more?
Oh, that. Sorry, I forgot. I was so busy, you know?
- Let's go home.
- Why?
To make more kimchi.
What?
Make more kimchi, then you can marry. Come out.
Buy some at the Korean market.
I don't eat kimchi that's not yours!
How do I look? Pretty?
Why are you dressed like that? I bought you a tux.
Didn't you get it?
Muhyeok!
Let go! Hold on!
Hey!
Hey! Ow! Let go!
Hey, let me go!
Muhyeok!
Let go!
My husband, Jason, can be very scary.
Being in a killer mob and all. Did I not tell you?
Turn the car around. Quit messing around.
Let's go to our country.
What?
Let's go to Korea. Let's live there.
There'll be a way for us there.
We'll be able to live well there. If we go there...
Turn the car around! I'm late to the wedding!
Let's go to our country!
Our country is here!
Danny, please! I'm sorry, okay? It's my fault.
It's my fault that I taught you
how to speak Korean, okay?
I'm sorry.
Then let's die!
If we can't live together then let's die together.
Muhyeok!
When I'm born again, I'll come back a rich man!
I'll become richer than Jason!
And I'll make you really happy!
Muhyeok!
Why are you doing this? Calm down!
Say your prayers, if you want to. For the last time.
Muhyeok! Why are you doing this?
Calm down.
I'm going...
I'll see you in the next life...
Oh, my. Oh...
Oh, my...
Oh, my god!
- South Korea.
- Okay, passenger name?
Song Eunchae.
[Start paying attenshun crazee brat]
- It's Kang Minju!
- She's so beautiful!
What's with you? Go slowly!
- Jason!
- Where were you?
I'm sorry. Are you mad? You alright?
I'm sorry, honey. It's okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go inside.
How sleazy.
I want some kimchi.
You may kiss the bride.
Muhyeok!
No!
[Episode 2 Preview]
I love you too, Eunchae.
I'll take responsibility for you.
[Sorry for saying I want to be with you]
[Together Forever]
You saved our lives, so I'm sorry this is all I can do.
[Love hurts like crazy]
[And so that pain]
Where's your dad?
I don't have a dad.
He has your mom's eyes.
Take me to my mother.
[Turned into revenge]